I'm Aoiluri, your February 26th caller. Hi, everyone.
Let's have fun. Bye bye. Bye bye.
Is this Aoil Radio? That's right.
We're not there yet.
I'm sorry. Not quite there yet.
Spread your legs and stretch out your chest.
All the way down to the tips of your fingers.
All the way down to the fingertips.
I'm failing.
Rehearsal is over.
We're done. How was it?
Here comes Ritchey!
I think I can see the real thing now.
I can see it.
About 2 hours left?
It's 1:30.
I'll see you at the venue later.
Bye bye.
I'll be there.
Three's up.
I can't open my eyes.
I have brown eyes.
It's your timing, Momoa-chan.
Hold on.
It'll be about three seconds after you press the button.
Three.
Ready?
What do you think?
I don't see him. Maybe he's not here. I haven't seen him.
Three's up.
Three yes.
I'm starting to make eye contact.
I've always liked you.
I've always liked your face.
I've been waiting for you
I've been waiting for your face to go round and round
Make me like you more
Even though I'm not good at love
Somewhere...
I have a one-sided love like a cartoon
I can't believe I'm alone
An urban legend
I believed it.
Timing
I learned and I was known
My personality
I'm more voluminous than before
One of these days, my friends and I
I'm a mess.
I can't fix it.
I'm starting to see eye to eye.
I've fallen in love with you.
I'm sure you'll make a funny face
I'm carrying my feelings
To the sky beyond
Covered by a hard bag
I wished I could be something
I had no reason to believe
Not here
I dreamed of somewhere else.
This world.
A little too bright.
I don't know if it's far
I can't see it.
Top of the line
You're not alone
Come on, let's go
Let's spread our wings
I'm still invisible
Small
Unreliable
Stupid
Arms...
I held your arm.
I could see.
I see you.
I could have wished for
Every day.
I got over it.
I realized how small I was
I was so frustrated
I grew a little taller
With you
It's about time
It's time for us
It's our turn.
Joy
Sadness.
Laughter.
Thank you for all your hard work
Use a lot of space
Okay, let's go to the first floor.
We'll use a lot of space
Okay, I'll take the bottom floor.
Up.
I'm in charge of the top and the bottom
The sides are difficult.
I'll probably be back soon.
I've finished taking pictures.I finished taking pictures.
lunch
Dinner
This is a beef bowl
and something like
and salmon.
Ah!
It's blue.
Blue.
This way, please.
Come on, everybody.
We're waiting.
We'll be waiting.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
I'm going to drink my favorite green tea.
I'm done with the benefit.
There's one more person who's done.
Here she is.
This is Seri and Aa-chan!
Chin-chin.
How was your day?
I knew it!
Are you talking about the benefit?
No, it's not.
The live show...
I've never seen you before.
Faces you've never seen before
There are so many
and
We didn't put them together by ourselves.
We're going to team up, aren't we?
Of course we would.
Setlist
That's why...
It's gonna be so much fun here.
They're gonna come next.
I'm so excited to be here!
And I'm a little hungry.
I'm hungry.
I don't know...
At the MC.
When I was drinking water at the MC...
I'm hungry.
I don't have any
I'll have some water.
I'm sure it's nothing.
I thought so, but it was fun.
But you know what?
It's nice to meet you.
It's true, I've never met you either.
Like this.
We have a good rapport.
What are you talking about, Moe-chan?
I'll keep working on your vocabulary, Moe-chan.
I'll work on it.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
What about the live show?
Seino
Center
bye-bye bye-bye
Thank you everyone!
The Yokohama concert on February 26th was a success!
I know my MC was not so good, but thank you so much for your warm support.
Thank you very much for your warm support.
It was a lot of fun!
See you again!